Yeah, no latency, a real
bitch be fucking with me
and shit, so I can't even
hear myself right now.
Niggas be talking shit, call my last track
a five.
I just be writing hits, cause that's what
I like.
I came out from the pits, that's where the
fuck niggas hide.
They call me on some shit
I press decline,
I press decline.
I'ma pick up, when the whole world is
mine.
They got opinions, I got dominion.
Soon they gon' turn, into my minions.
I'm laughing and whistling, from pole
position.
We all rats in this shit, racing to
finish.
But I be doing, not thinking.
Asking you what it do, what you think,
man.
You ain't like what I do, think I'm shit,
I fuck with my shit cause it's stinky.
It's a different aroma to me.
It's smelling like victory.
You ain't liking my energy.
But it's cooler than you'll ever be.
Put down the phone, your number delete.
I press decline.
Put down the phone, your number
I'ma pick up.
When the whole world is...
When the whole world is mine.
Go call your girl, bitch.